# BANDA JAGDISH SHIVSHANKAR

jagdish.banda@gmail.com | M: 9033283754 | Sr. Software Engineer – Web | Ahmedabad

Dear Sir/Madam,

You are looking for someone who can work in a wide range of programming languages and manage project deliveries, Better client communication and that is exactly what I am looking for. As Web Developer, I work with organization to develop scopes and manage project milestones. I am expertise with 3 year's experience in **NodeJS**, 3 years in **PHP**, and 3 months in **ReactJS**.

I look forward to meeting with you and discuss the details of this position. In this meantime, please find my "Curriculum Vitae" in next page.

Sincerely,

Jagdish Banda

### BANDA JAGDISH SHIVSHANKAR

# Sr. Software Engineer - Web

E-mail: jagdish.banda@gmail.com

Mobile: 9033283754

Remote Profile: My Full Profile & Portfolio

"Enthusiastic software engineer with 6+ year's experience participating in the complete product development lifecycle of Applications. I am a driven individual with the ability to adapt to any situation and proven potential to grow self and others."

#### INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Self-confident and able to learn new technologies
- Responsible attitude aimed at ensuring positive outcomes of assigned tasks
- Good client communication, Collaboration, Leadership, Presenter, Team-work
- Proficient in system design, testing, debugging, documentation

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

# Web Development:

- PHP (Codeignitor, Laravel, Wordpress)
- NodeJS (ExpressJS, Serverless, AWS Lambda, AdonisJS, SailsJS)
- ReactJS

#### Database:

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB

## Other Utilities:

Agile, Blockchain Technology, GIT Version Control, Slack, Basecamp, Trello

# **PROJECT HISTORY**

I have worked in many projects in the past and some are ongoing. I am mentioning recent projects but we can discuss others in interview, if i shortlisted.

### **TOLLGURU**

Tollguru mapping service is designed for real America - where both costs and times figure in route decisions. Tollguru shows you cheaper routes not shown by any other mapping applications such as Google maps, HERE maps, Openstreep maps.

Technology: AngularJS, NodeJS, AWS Lambda function, Serverless, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB

URL: https://tollguru.com

#### **KNEEBU**

It offer services on-demand or whenever it's convenient for you. Once the Provider (host) accepts your request to rent, you can connect instantly with the Provider via chat.

Technology: PHP Laravel, MySQL

URL: https://kneebu.com

#### **FALDAX**

FALDAX is the cryptocurrency exchange to trade the world's largest cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ripple, Ethereum, ERC-20 token etc.

Technology: NodeJS, SailsJS, ExpressJS, ReactJS, PostgreSQL, RabitMQ

URL: https://www.faldax.com

#### **CAREER HISTORY**

# January 2019 to Present

OpenXcell Technolabs, Ahmedabad

Sr. Software Engineer

- Got chance to work in blockchain technology
- Responsible to develop webservices, Admin Panel
- Responsible to teach and train fresher's
- AWS Create Lambda functions, Serverless
- Got chance to work in Dedicated project

# November 2015 - December 2018

Technostacks InfoTech PVT Ltd, Ahmedabad

PHP/NodeJS Developer

- Responsible for develop/customize Wordpress plugins
- Responsible for develop webservices
- Develop and customize Wordpress theme
- Develop Admin panel and websites
- AWS EC2/RDS Setup, Configure API Gateway, Creating Lambda function in NodeJS
- R&D for new technology as per client requirement

## **July 2014 - November 2015**

iZone Technology, Ahmedabad

Jr. PHP/Wordpress Developer

- Starting here as my first level of career. I am working as Core PHP, Wordpress developer here.
- Responsible for Web design with Photoshop and Fireworks from PSD or as client requirements
- Convert PSD to Wordpress/html
- Convert older sites to Responsive Design

# **INTERESTS/HOBBIES**

- I like to play cricket, hanging out with friends, watching movies
- Like to learn new technologies whatever, not only related to professional career
- Mobile Game seeker (PUBG, COD, etc...)
- Spend the time with families and trips, Take participate in various activities

# **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

My all academic performances are mentioned below:

COURCE	YEAR	BOARD/UNIVERSITY	RESULT
B.E. (Computers)	July-2014	G.T.U	7.7 CPI
Diploma	June-2011	G.T.U	7.8 CPI
H.S.C(Science)	March-2008	H.S.E.B	58.00 %
S.S.C	March-2006	G.S.E.B	76.86 %

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Full Name : Banda Jagdish Shivshankar

E-mail : jagdish.banda@gmail.com

Address : Odhav, Ahmedabad

Date of Birth : 08/04/1991

Nationality : Indian (Hindu)

Mother Tongue : Kannada

Language Known : Hindi, Kannada, Gujarati, Telugu, English

#### **DECLARATION**

I do hereby declare that the above written particulars are authentic as per my Knowledge and belief. So, please response well to me.

PLACE: Ahmedabad

Jagdish S. Banda

DATE:

(Signature)